Udududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududududud
There's nothing left to do,
but bring this game to an end.
It should have been done ages ago,
but I'll finally be rid of
you Joestars once and for all.
Using the power of my stand, I
will send you all into oblivion!
Now the world will stop time itself!
Thank you.
End of the world!
That's the secret?
Jotaro, your exasperating family line is
just moments away from being eradicated.
My hundred-year struggle with
the Josars ends with you.
Begone!
He moved his finger. But how?
What's going on?
He shouldn't be able to
think, let alone move.
Wait, there's no way.
Is his power the same as the world's?
Your Stan has a lot in
common with my Star Platinum.
Did he mean the World and Star
Platinum are the same type of stand?
Damn it.
Can you see me right now?
Are you consciously moving, or
is it an involuntary twitch?
Okay, time's up.
Jotaro, could you see me?
Must I repeat?
I asked if you could follow my movements!
See why?
You're not making sense.
Need to have your eyes checked, Dio.
Just you wait!
You can't run forever!
Seeing me isn't going to do you any
good when time is standing still!
If your Stone does bear
similarities to mine, prove it!
I want to see just how
much we have in common!
Yes.
It's been six months since I began
to grasp the art of stopping time.
To test the world's speed and power, I
commanded my servant to take aim point-blank,
right at my back.
And for a moment, it looked as
though time itself had stood still.
I thought for sure I was hallucinating.
It seemed like the vision a boxer has when
his opponent's punches linger in mid-air.
That second felt like an eternity.
But I wasn't simply imagining things.
My stand was actually
able to move between the
hovering bullets that
were suspended in time.
And it could grasp them.
Yes, Lord Dio.
You are well on your way to
being the master of time.
The next step is willing yourself to
move through the realm of frozen time.
It must happen as naturally as breathing?
Or as nonchalantly as snapping a pencil!
betwixt your mighty fingers.
You must think of it
as completely ordinary.
The most important thing is
having faith in yourself.
It's imperative that you find the
mental fortitude to steal your mind.
You are the one true ruler of this world.
Controlling time should
be second nature to you.
Then one day, I sensed the wheels of time
and the world interlock at long last.
Like a ray of clarity dispersing the
shadows in my mind, a revelation befell me.
I was Dio, and my destiny was to surpass
all living things, including stand users!
I can stop time for five seconds, and the
time limit keeps extending by the day!
Now, Jotaro, you're about to
experience just how weak you are!
Time to make good on my promise!
The world grinds to a halt!
I see you planted a magnet.
Must have been when we
were exchanging blows.
It looks like a wallet magnet or
one picked from a pocket planner.
I have to admit, you had me fooled.
You're a clever boy indeed.
But!
If you have to resort to
inane tricks like that?
It only proves that you can't
move while time is standing still.
You've only postponed the
inevitable by a few seconds.
This is the end!
Die, Jotaro!
What?
Oh, no.
He's moving.
What nerve.
Although, he can only do it briefly.
The magnet wasn't meant to
make me think he could move.
It was made to make me think he couldn't.
Damn it, it was a trap
designed to lure me in.
And I fell for it.
The key is believing that your
power is completely ordinary.
Disgusting.
To think that my domain could be invaded,
and by one of the Joestars, no less.
It's infuriating.
I was able to move for a second
there that's a good sign even so
that's not much it would only give
me enough time for a single punch?
You there, woman.
How about you make yourself
useful and fetch me my leg?
Bring it here this instant!
Imagine you're a flight
attendant bringing caviar to
a passenger in first class
if it gets you here faster!
Well that's good to
know seems I'll have to
blow your head off to do
any significant damage!
Bastard you've already siphoned
off enough energy to heal yourself!
It's like that gaping hole I opened
in your gut was never even there!
Your eyes followed me
even while time was frozen
which confirms that you
can see my movements?
Isn't that right, Jotaro?
Nervous yet, sweetheart? Not at all.
Kakyoin did you quite the favor.
Because of his brilliant mind, he was able
to correctly deduce the world's secret.
And because he passed
that knowledge along,
you figured out that I
could stop time at will
and worked until you learned
how to do it yourself.
Then again,
you haven't had as much
training as I have,
so I'm curious to know exactly how
long you can move while time is frozen.
Two seconds? Or maybe three?
Or perhaps you can move
five seconds like me,
but you're pretending you can't
to gain some kind of an advantage.
Clever.
Which is it?
This isn't good.
I could probably move longer if I
was able to get some practice in.
But as it stands, the
best I can do is a second.
If I was forced to make a guess, I'd
say you could only move for a second.
Be that as it may, you've still
managed to infiltrate my world.
Only a fool would risk
approaching you now,
and though I'm many things, a fool
wouldn't be considered one of them.
While it's achingly clear that my
advantage over you is overwhelming,
I've still devised a way to execute you,
so regardless of how long you can move in
my world, you'll never escape your demise!
You're white as a sheet.
Do these bring back memories?
Do they remind you that
you're going to die a death
even more horrific than
your pathetic grandfather?
Screw this bastard.
How the hell does he come
up with this kind of shit?
I need to be careful.
There is no escape.
The world!
Five seconds left.
Do you think your star platinum can deflect
all of the knives once time resumes?
If I were a betting man, I'd give that
plan a one in a million chance of working.
Four seconds!
It must be terrifying to stare death
in the face and be helpless to stop it!
Only three seconds remain!
You're down to two
seconds are you telling me
that's the best you've
got that's just more!
Evidence of your ineptitude
in the presence of
one such as myself one
second left to go zero?
It's over.
But one can never be too careful.
Now, to be perfectly honest,
I'm relieved I was able to do
away with you so quickly, Chotaro.
I have to say,
I never would have thought that you'd have
the power or to infiltrate
my perfect world.
Now, let's see.
A fitting analogy would be the automobile.
Useful machines until the roads
become clogged with them all.
Sorry, but the mantle of Master
of Time is reserved for me alone.
Oh, good grief.
He'd throw enough knives or what?
I mean, he'd turn my favorite
uniform into Swiss cheese.
Well, I'm glad I decided to
stuff my clothes with magazines.
I figured it was only a matter of
time before he tried throwing weapons,
but I didn't expect that many.
My best bet right now
is to play possum and
wait for a chance to take Dio by surprise.
Since he can regenerate, I've got to bash
his brains in, or else he'll never die.
I believe I'll do one more
check for good measure.
The Joestars have a way of
coming back from the dead.
And there's a chance Jotaro
is putting on this death act.
I need to make sure he's gone.
For good.
I'll use this to sever that
troublesome head of his!
It's time for you to die!
Shotaro!
The only one dying here is you!
You're the one who's gonna die! Polnareff!
Time has stopped.
Let's get a good look at your face.
I see it's Polnareff and
now time will resume.
What a shame Polnareff you were
so close but dropped the ball!
If you'd lunged with more force
behind your attack You could
have eviscerated my brain beyond
the point of regeneration?
You bastard!
It's not over yet.
When will you all accept
that you cannot kill me?
You are nothing more than pawns
destined to be put in check.
Your death brings about the end of
the Joestar's tragic Egyptian journey.
Damn it.
If I don't do something,
Polnareff's as good as dead.
I was gonna keep up this act until I had a
chance to catch him off
guard and crush his skull.
But saving Polnareff
from this United freak is
more important right now
it's not gonna be easy.
Though he won't make
the mistake of crossing
into Star Platinum's
range so it'll just end up
like The last time he
trapped me whatever I do I
can't let him know I'm
alive as long as he thinks
I'm Dead I have the
element of surprise which
gives me a chance to get
in close strange how things
End up coming full circle
one minute I'm trying
to will myself to move
through a world of frozen
in time.
And the next I'm doing everything
I can to stay completely still.
Enjoy your journey to the afterlife!
Damn you, Jotaro.
Was he alive all along?
At the very least, he
seems to be coming too.
Hold it!
This is the police!
You try anything funny and we will shoot!
Slowly put your hands in the air!
Ah, what impeccable timing.
If you wouldn't mind, there's
somebody I'd like for you to shoot.
Do you see that man lying on the ground?
Shoot his leg or torso.
That's right, line up the
shot and let the bullet fly.
I thought I heard Jotaro
make a sound a moment ago,
but I guess my mind was
playing tricks on me.
Could he be any more demented?
He's at least lost interest in Polnareff.
But now that his attention's back
on me, he's even more suspicious.
He's not gonna rest
until he's sure I'm dead.
Things just got a lot harder.
I know.
Why don't we check his breathing?
No luck.
He's not breathing.
But there's no way to hide his heartbeat.
Shit this hurts!
If I black out, everything we've been
through will have been for nothing.
Dying because I use my
own stand to stop my
heart it'd be ironic in
a morbid kind of way.
And sure enough there's no heartbeat.
What do you know?
I suppose the thought of him being alive
was just a figment of my imagination.
Those stranger things have happened.
So I should still probably
lop off his head to be sure.
That's not a problem, is it?
What?
I have to stop time again!
The world!
I gotta hand it to you.
You really put me through hell back there.
You're not stopping time or
leaving with your skull intact.
Got it?
No!
This can't be happening to me!
Took long enough I finally got to run my
fist straight through his demented skull.
But that walking cesspool of evil lived at
the bottom of the sea for over a century.
I can't be sure that attack killed him
it's a bit too early to take a victory lap.
I will annihilate you.
What the hell?
I can't move!
Jotaro, what did you do to me?
I don't have control over my legs!
I can't even stand!
My head!
The pain is unbearable!
I think I'm going to vomit!
This can't be happening to me!
I'm the pinnacle of perfection!
He actually damaged my
brain and paralyzed my legs!
Shit, shit, shit!
I've got to find a way out of here!
I've doused you with
gasoline so you can't hide.
Normally, I would hate to kick a
guy when he's down on his luck.
But with you, I don't give a damn.
You killed my friends and
countless innocent bystanders.
So don't expect any mercy.
Ha ha ha ha!
Ah ha!
Come forth!
The world!
If I can...
Just...
make it a little farther...
And now, time will flow as usual!
While he had his ear to the ground, he
was also listening for any nearby cars.
Clever, but...
Bastard's not getting away that easily!
Almost!
Keep going!
That's it!
I'm almost there!
And where do you think you're going?
We've got unfinished business.
It's over, Dio.
Time to accept it!
No, no, no, no!
You fell for it, Chotaro.
Now my victory is all but assured.
Once again, my genius
has triumphed over you.
Doesn't this street look familiar?
This street.
What have I done?
You failed.
This was my escape route
to your grandfather.
And now his blood is mine!
T .O.
You're dead!
Jotaro.
It's been quite the journey, eh, my boy?
The blood of the Joestars
courses through my veins!
This whole thing might have ended
differently, but you wouldn't piss me off.